A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.108: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1980-2013; AC_2013_108; 27.51 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R4365-R4385; 21 standard record storage boxes, R4365-R4385
  - INV, AC_2013_108_16; 2.83 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes and 1 oversize box
    - 2009 INV 325 - ALLAVIDA KENYA - KENYA SOCIAL INVESTMENT EXCHANGE, 2009-2012 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 326 - ALLIANCE FOR A GREEN REVOLUTION IN AFRICA (KENYA) - IMPACT INVESTING GUARANTEE FUND FOR SMALLHOLDER FARMERS, 2009-2011 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 327 - CLEAN ECONOMY NETWORK FOUNDATION - BUSINESS PLAN DEVELOPMENT, 2009-2011 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 328 - ROCKEFELLER PHILANTHROPY ADVISORS - MONOGRAPH ON BEST PRACTICES IN IMPACT INVESTING, 2009-2010 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 328 - Solutions for Impact Investors: From Strategy to Implemenation - Published Material, 2009-2010; 2013:108:005 (Box SF 1)
    - 2009 INV 329 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF SINGAPORE - VALUING SOCIAL ENTERPRISES IN ASIA, 2009-2011 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 331 - AFRICA AGRICULTURE DEVELOPMENT COMPANY (ENGLAND) - SUSTAINABLE AGRI-BUSINESS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2009-2011 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 332 - HOPE CONSULTING - MONEY FOR GOOD INITIATIVE, 2009-2010 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 333 - CAPITAL MARKETS AUTHORITY (KENYA) - IMPACT INVESTMENT OPPORTUNITIES FOR EAST AFRICA, 2009-2011 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 INV 335 - WILLIAM J. CLINTON FOUNDATION - 5TH CLINTON GLOBAL INITIATIVE CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4381)
  - OAF, AC_2013_108_17; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2009 OAF 301 - AFRICA HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT INTERNATIONAL (KENYA) - CONFERENCE ON ETHNIC DIVERSITY IN EASTERN AFRICA, 2009-2010 (Box R4381)
    - 2009 OAF301 - Ethnic Diversity in Eastern Africa: Opportunities and Challenges - Published Material, 2009-2010; 2013:108:004 (Item 2013:108:004)
    - 2009 OAF 302 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - SURVEY IN E. AFRICA TO EXPLORE FEASIBILITY OF UTILIZING RETIRED PROFESSORS FOR TRAINING AND MENTORING, 2009-2012 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OAF 303 - A24 MEDIA (MAURITIUS) - DOCUMENTARY FILMS ON SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OAF 304 - AFRICAN ECONOMIC RESEARCH CONSORTIUM (KENYA) - MAP ORGANIZATIONS AND INITIATIVES IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2009-2011 (Box R4382)
  - OAS, AC_2013_108_18; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 OAS 302 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - SYMPOSIUM, "MUSLIM IN THAILAND" (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OAS 303 - THAILAND DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOUNDATION - IMPACT OF GLOBAL CRISIS ON THAIS, 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OAS 304 - ASIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - TRANSITIONS IN ASIAN AGRICULTURE, 2009-2011 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OAS 305 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH POLICY PROGRAM (THAILAND) - 4TH ASIA-PACIFIC ACTION ALLIANCE ON HUMAN RESOURCES FOR HEALTH CONFERENCE (Box R4382)
  - OPP, AC_2013_108_19; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 OPP 305 - MANHATTAN INSTITUTE FOR POLICY RESEARCH - CONFERENCE, "THINKING BIG, NEW YORK AND LONDON...", 2009-2011 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 306 - V-DAY - PLAY, "SWIMMING UPSTREAM", 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 306 - Raw Footage Interviews from "Let Freedom Swing: A Celebration of America" - Digital Material, 2009-2010; 2013:108:013-2013:108:019 (Item 2013:108:013-2013:108:019)
    - 2009 OPP 306 - Highlight Reel of "Let Freedom Swing: A Celebration of America" - Digital Material, 2009-2010; 2013:108:020-2013:108:026 (Item 2013:108:020-2013:108:026)
    - 2009 OPP 307 - GRANTMAKERS IN THE ARTS - 2009 ANNUAL CONFERENCE, "NAVIGATING THE ART OF CHANGE", 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 308 - NEW YORK CITY PARTNERSHIP FOUNDATION - AFFORDABLE MULTI-FAMILY RESIDENTIAL PROPERTIES, 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 309 - TECTONIC THEATER PROJECT - EXPLORATION OF "THE LARAMIE PROJECT", 2008-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 310 - JAZZ AT LINCOLN CENTER - CONCERT, "JAZZ AND CIVICS...", 2008-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 310 - "Let Freedom Swing: A Celebration of America" Highlight Reel - Digital Material, 2008-2010; 2013:108:027 (Item 2013:108:027)
    - 2009 OPP 311 - FEMINEST PRESS -" WOMEN WRITING AFRICA" TRAVEL SUPPORT, 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
    - 2009 OPP 312 - DANCE THEATRE OF HARLEM - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2010 (Box R4382)
  - ORC, AC_2013_108_21; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 ORC 301 - ASIA FOUNDATION - GLOBAL ECONOMIC CRISIS ALLEVIATION IN VIETNAM AND THAILAND, 2009-2012 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 ORC 302 - LIVING CITIES, INC. - WORKSHOP ON NEIGHBORHOOD STABILIZATION PROGRAM, 2009-2010 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 ORC 303 - NEIGHBORWORKS AMERICA - FEDERAL MORTGAGE ASSISTANCE PROGRAM, 2009-2011 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 ORC 304 - FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION (ITALY) - LIVELIHOOD SUPPORT FOR EASTERN AFRICA, 2009-2011 (Box R4383)
  - PHS, AC_2013_108_22; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 PHS 305 - INDEPENDENT SECTOR - ENVISIONING OUR FUTURE INITIATIVE, 2009-2010 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 PHS 310 - ASIAN AMERICANS/PACIFIC ISLANDERS IN PHILANTHROPY (AAPIP) - GENERAL OPERATING EXPENSES (2 FOLDERS), 1994-2010 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 PHS 311 - NATIONAL VIDEO RESOURCES - PHILANTHROPY'S MOVING IMAGE: A CELEBRATION OF FILM, VIDEO AND TELEVISION FUNDING, 2001-2010 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 PHS 313 - PHILANTHROPY NEW YORK - PUBLIC POLICY INITIATIVE, 2009-2011 (Box R4383)
    - 2009 PHS 317 - COUNCIL ON FOUNDATIONS - 2009 COMMUNITY FOUNDATIONS CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4383)
  - PRE, AC_2013_108_23; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 PRE 301 - ADMINISTRATION OF MUNICIPAL EDUCATION "VELSKOE" (RUSSIA) - 110TH ANNIVERSARY OF GEORGII KARPECHENKO, CONFERENCE (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 302 - SOCIETY OF BEHAVIORAL MEDICINE - 11TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF BEHAVIORAL MEDICINE, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 303 - DEMOCRACY 21 EDUCATION FUND - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 304 - HUDSON RIVER FOUNDATION - CREATING A VISION FOR THE HUDSON RIVER VALLEY PROJECT, 2009-2012 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 305 - CAMBRIDGE UNIVERSITY PRESS AMERICAN BRANCH - PUBLICATION ENTITLED, "WEALTH, HEALTH and DEMOCRACY IN EAST ASIA AND LATIN AMERICA", 2009-2011 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 306 - FOUNDATION FOR ART AND PRESERVATION IN EMBASSIES - ART FOR THE U.S MISSION TO THE U.N., 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 307 - AMERICA'S PROMISE ALLIANCE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2011 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 308 - COMMUNICATIONS CONSORTIUM MEDIA CENTER - UN CEDAW COMMUNICATIONS, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 310 - AMIGOS DEL MUSEO DEL BARRIO - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 312 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - PAKISTAN/AFGHANISTAN PROJECTS, 2009-2012 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 312 - Independent Task Force Report No. 65 U.S. Strategy for Pakistan and Afghanistan - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2013:108:028 (Item 2013:108:028)
    - 2009 PRE 314 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - PRESIDENT'S COUNCIL OF ADVISORS ON SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY MEETINGS, 2009-2012 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 PRE 315 - SECURITY COUNCIL REPORT - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2004-2011 (Box R4384)
  - RES, AC_2013_108_24; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2009 RES 301 - ENERGY AND RESOURCE INSTITUTE (INDIA) - 2009 DELHI SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT SUMMIT, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 RES 302 - MILLENNIUM PROJECT CORPORATION - CONFERENCE ON IMPROVING RESEARCH CAPACITY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 RES 303 - UNITED NATIONS UNIVERSITY (JAPAN) - ROUNDTABLE AND EXPERT WORKSHOP ON ENVIRONMENTAL MIGRATION, 2009-2010 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 RES 309 - RAND CORPORATION - MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING ON POVERTY AND HUMAN DEVELOPMENT, 2009-2012 (Box R4384)
    - 2009 RES 310 - SOCIETY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT (ITALY) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, AND BC CONFERENCE, 2009-2012 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 RES 311 - INSTITUTE OF ECONOMIC AFFAIRS (KENYA) - YOUTH SCENARIOS PROJECT (2 FOLDERS), 2009-2012 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 RES 311 - Youth Research Compendium - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2013:108:007 (Item 2013:108:007)
    - 2009 RES311 - Youth Fact Book: Infinite Possibility or Definite Disaster - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2013:108:008 (Item 2013:108:008)
    - 2009 RES 311 - Keys: Kenya Youth Scenarios - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2013:108:009 (Item 2013:108:009)
    - 2009 RES 313 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY POLICY AND STRATEGY STUDIES (VIETNAM) - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING RESEARCH, 2009-2011 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 RES 313 - Scanning Science and Technology Trends in Asia-Pacific - Published Material, 2009-2011; 2013:108:006 (Item 2013:108:006)
  - SCG, AC_2013_108_25; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 SCG 301 - UNITED STATES ARTISTS - "USA ROCKEFELLER FELLOWS"; USA BERRESFORD FELLOW", 2009-2013 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 SCG 302 - AFRICAN POPULATION AND HEALTH RESEARCH CENTRE (KENYA) - CORE SUPPORT, 2001-2012 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 SCG 303 - UNITED STATES DEPARTMENT OF STATE - SECRETARY'S INNOVATION AWARD FOR WOMEN'S AND GIRLS' EMPOWERMENT, 2009-2012 (Box R4385)
  - Search (SRC), AC_2013_108_26; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2009 SRC 101 - SMART GROWTH AMERICA - COORDINATED STATE ADVOCACY CAMPAIGN, 2008-2009 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 SRC 102 - CITISTATES GROUP - "CENTURY OF THE CITY" PUBLICATION, 2008-2009 (Box R4385)
    - 2009 SRC 103 - TRUST FOR INDIGENOUS CULTURE AND HEALTH (KENYA) - URBAN HEALTH, 2008-2010 (Box R4385)